<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Brodie Blog</title>
    <link>http://brodie.cookwithchef.com/tags/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Brodie Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 17:23:50 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://brodie.cookwithchef.com/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog 2019</title>
      <link>http://brodie.cookwithchef.com/posts/blog/blog_2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 17:23:50 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brodie.cookwithchef.com/posts/blog/blog_2019/</guid>
      <description>Here We Go Again Just like last year, I&amp;rsquo;ve been getting that urge to start keep a blog again. This year, I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to clean up a few things with the process! I&amp;rsquo;ve switched to using Hugo to generate a static site. It&amp;rsquo;s a lot more full featured than my hacked together generator in C. Switching to Hugo means that I&amp;rsquo;ll have pagination without having to write it myself. It also means that I can switch to using markdown to write posts!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Blog 2018</title>
      <link>http://brodie.cookwithchef.com/posts/blog/blog_2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brodie.cookwithchef.com/posts/blog/blog_2018/</guid>
      <description>This week I&#39;ve been working on yet another new blog. It feels a little silly, since I never manage to keep up with writing entries, but maybe this time will be different. It&#39;s also a very small enjoyable project that I can finish and cross off the list. The current version feels pretty similar to last time, but the trick is that this time I&#39;m statically generating the pages offline in C++.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Does This Work Again?</title>
      <link>http://brodie.cookwithchef.com/posts/blog/forget/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brodie.cookwithchef.com/posts/blog/forget/</guid>
      <description>I haven&#39;t written anything for this blog in a while, so I forget how it was working. Maybe I should further document my process! It occurs to me that I have a few posts about this blog, but nothing seriously describing what it is or how it works! I also forget my password.  Entries are written in HTML with a few meta tags at the top. These can then be FTP&#39;d to the server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Markdown!</title>
      <link>http://brodie.cookwithchef.com/posts/blog/no_markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brodie.cookwithchef.com/posts/blog/no_markdown/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I decided that it would be really nice if I could edit my posts in markdown. There are definitely some easy to find php libraries for parsing markdown, so I didn&#39;t think it would be too much work. This morning, however, integrating a library in seemed like it was going to be just a little too much busy work.
Instead, how good is sublime at editing HTML? I installed the Emmet plug in, which does some pretty cool stuff, but it&#39;s overkill.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>